A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Long-Range Planning Committee, 1991-1992, TD(14) (Box-folder 028:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Administrators, 1991-1992, TD(5), AD(2) (Box-folder 028:028)
  Reports, Letters, Contract For Administrative Services
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Continuing Education, 1991-1992, TD(8), AD(3) (Box-folder 028:029)
  Continuing Education Hours, Letter, Meeting Minute, Program Contact List, Evaluation Agreement, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Legislation, 1991-1992, TD, Newsletters(6), Photocopies of Newspaper Articles(8), AD(1), Bylaw (Box-folder 028:030)
  Mailing List, Memorandum, Reports, Memorandum, Letters, Flyers
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nutrition services Payment Systems(NSPS), 1991-1992, TD(48) (Box-folder 029:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Professional Recognition, 1991-1992, TD(19) (Box-folder 029:002)
  Guideline, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations Media Representative, 1991-1992, TD(4) (Box-folder 029:003)
  Reports, Letter, Evaluation Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Annual Meetings, 1991-1992, TD(27), AD(2), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 029:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1991-1992, TD(1) (Box-folder 029:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Teller's Committee, 1991-1992, TD(1) (Box-folder 029:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Lines, 1991-1992, TD(4), Newsletters(5) (Box-folder 029:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affirmative Action Committee, 1991-1992, TD(30), AD(1), Flyer(1), Transparency(1) (Box-folder 029:008)
  Reports, Letters, Memorandum, Norfolk State University Prpgram Mentorship Reporting Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Professional Recruitment Coordinator(SPRC), 1991-1992, TD(38), Photocopies of Journal Article(5) (Box-folder 029:009)
  Reports, Letters, Quarterly Report Forms,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian Award, 1991-1992, TD(3) (Box-folder 029:010)
  Memorandum, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Scholarships, 1991-1992, TD(2) (Box-folder 029:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: District Reports, 1991-1992, TD(15), AD(1) (Box-folder 029:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Dietetic Technicians, 1991-1992, TD(6) (Box-folder 029:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Kathryn Smith Award, 1991-1992, TD(1) (Box-folder 029:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Awards and Scholarship, 1991-1992, TD(6) (Box-folder 029:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1991-1992, TD(3), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 029:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Alliances, 1991-1992, TD(31), AD(1), Brochure(3), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 029:017)
  Reports, Letters, Continuing Education Prior Approval Request Form,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence, 1991-1992, TD(77), AD(2), Newsletters(4), Name Card(1), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 029:018)
  Reports, Letters, Membership Roster, Suggestion Sheet,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Treasurer's Financial Reports, 1992-1993, TD(51) (Box-folder 030:001)
  Reports, Bylaw
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: VDA Meetings, 1992-1993, TD(3) (Box-folder 030:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Delegates Reports, 1992-1993, TD(20) (Box-folder 030:003)
  Reports, Letters, Flyer
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Nomination Report, 1992-1993, TD(2) (Box-folder 030:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Public Relations, 1992-1993, TD(28) (Box-folder 030:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Media Representatives, 1992-1993, TD(58) (Box-folder 030:006)
  Activity Report Forms, Letters, Memorandum, Flyer, Evaluation Form, CV, Reports,
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Finance Committee Meetings, 1992-1993, TD(13) (Box-folder 030:007)
  Memorandum, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1992-1993, TD(6) (Box-folder 030:008)
  Memorandum, Grant Application Form, Report, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1992-1993, TD(17) (Box-folder 030:009)
  Bylaws, Reports, Executive Board Memberships
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Agenda, 1992-1993, TD(12) (Box-folder 030:010)
  Letters, Meeting Reports,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Minutes, 1992-1993, TD(20) (Box-folder 030:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board List, 1992-1993, TD(5) (Box-folder 030:012)
  Letter, Bylaw Revisions
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Administrator, 1992-1993, TD(23) (Box-folder 030:013)
  Letters, Job Description, Contract, Reports, Organization Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Publications, 1992-1993, TD(7) (Box-folder 030:014)
  Memorandum, Report, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1992-1993, TD(13), AD(1) (Box-folder 030:015)
  Evaluation Forms, Program HoursReports, Letters, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Nominations and Awards, 1992-1993, TD(25) (Box-folder 030:016)
  Reports, Letters, 1993 Ballot Information
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Scholarships and Awards, 1992-1993, TD(4) (Box-folder 030:017)
  Memorandum, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian Award, 1992-1993, TD(11) (Box-folder 030:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1992-1993, TD(48) (Box-folder 030:019)
  Reports, Letters, Membership Contact Lists, Senate Bill No.506
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Professional Recognition, 1992-1993, TD(40) (Box-folder 030:020)
  Letters, Position Announcement, Memorandum, Recommendatio Form, Reports,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS Committee Meeting, 1992-1993, TD(6) (Box-folder 030:021)
  Reports, Letter, Flyer
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Plan, 1992-1993, TD(3) (Box-folder 030:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation (ADAF), 1992-1993, TD(8), AD(2) (Box-folder 030:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Division Reports, 1992-1993, TD(31) (Box-folder 030:024)
  Reports, Letters, RYDY Program Guideline
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge Dietetic Association Reports, 1992-1993, TD(3) (Box-folder 030:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association Reports, 1992-1993, TD(3), AD(1) (Box-folder 030:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association Report, 1992-1993, TD(1) (Box-folder 030:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Southwest Dietetic Association Reports, 1992-1993, TD(3), AD(1) (Box-folder 030:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Dietetic Technicians, 1992-1993, TD(4) (Box-folder 030:029)
  Reports, Survey Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Professional Recruitment Coordinator (SPRC), 1992-1993, TD(21), AD(1), Flyers(3) (Box-folder 030:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affirmative Action Committee Reports, 1992-1993, TD(4) (Box-folder 030:031)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association Reports, 1992-1993, TD(4) (Box-folder 030:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Reports, 1992-1993, TD(4) (Box-folder 030:033)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Membership Survey, 1992-1993, TD(7), Survey Form (Box-folder 030:034)
  Reports, Letters, Survey for the VDA
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Nutrition Month Coalition, 1992-1993, TD(17), AD(1), Bookmarks(2) (Box-folder 030:035)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Restaurant Association, 1992-1993, TD(11), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 030:036)
  Reports, Letters, Participants Lists
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Health Council, 1992-1993, TD(16), Newsletter(2) (Box-folder 030:037)
  Reports, Letters, Report
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professionals (VAAHP), 1992-1993, TD(9) (Box-folder 030:038)
  Reports, Letters, Memorandum, Minutes
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Congress of Health Care Providers, 1992-1993, TD(15) (Box-folder 030:039)
  Reports, Letters, Minutes, Membership Listing
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1993-1994, TD(4) (Box-folder 031:001)
  Letters, Reports, Membership List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Agenda, 1993-1994, TD(12), AD(1) (Box-folder 031:002)
  Master Calendar, Meeting Agenda Planner, Minutes, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Minutes, 1993-1994, TD(24) (Box-folder 031:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Treasurer's Meetings, 1993-1994, TD(10) (Box-folder 031:004)
  Meeting Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Financial Committee, 1993-1994, TD(18), AD(16), Envelope(1) (Box-folder 031:005)
  Letters, Minutes, Financial Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Plans, 1993-1994, TD(7) (Box-folder 031:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADAF(American Dietetic Association Foundation), 1993-1994, TD(13), Booklets(2) (Box-folder 031:007)
  Letters, Declaration of Intent Form, Legacy Program Questions and Answers, Memorandum, Nomination Consent Form, Annual Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Meetings, 1993-1994, TD(29), AD(2), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 031:008)
  Conference Schedule, Letters, Minutes
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegate Reports, 1993-1994, TD(23) (Box-folder 031:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nomination Report, 1993-1994, TD(1) (Box-folder 031:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Media Representatives, 1993-1994, TD(20), AD(4) (Box-folder 031:011)
  Reports, Letters, Photocopy of Certificate of Recognition, List of Contacts, Activity Report
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations Reports, 1993-1994, TD(2) (Box-folder 031:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1993-1994, TD(5) (Box-folder 031:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1993-1994, TD(12) (Box-folder 031:014)
  Bylaws, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Administrative Report, 1993-1994, TD(2) (Box-folder 031:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Publications, 1993-1994, TD(2) (Box-folder 031:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1993-1994, TD(20), Pamphlet(1), Booklets(2) (Box-folder 031:017)
  Letters, Registration Form, Examination Handbooks, CDR Registration Forms, Articles, Reports, Continuing Education Program Hours
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Nominations and Awards, 1993-1994, TD(19) (Box-folder 031:018)
  Letters, Meeting Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Scholarship and Awards, 1993-1994, TD(24) (Box-folder 031:019)
  Scholarship Application Forms, Letters, Photocopies of Student Permanent Records, Guidelines for Application Evaluation
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1993-1994, TD(58) (Box-folder 031:020)
  Letters, Sample of Telephone Script, Meeting Reports, Federal Legislative Contacts, House of Deligates Committee Assignments, Symposium Registration Information, Award Participating Form, 1994 House of Delegates List, Reports, Special Project Funding Survey, Pamphlet, Journal Article, Contact Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS, 1993-1994, TD(11) (Box-folder 031:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Division Reports, 1993-1994, TD(40) (Box-folder 031:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge, 1993-1994, TD(2), AD(1) (Box-folder 031:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1993-1994, TD(3) (Box-folder 031:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association, 1993-1994, TD(7) (Box-folder 031:025)
  Reports, Letters, RDA Membership Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Southwest Dietetic Association, 1993-1994, TD(7) (Box-folder 031:026)
  Reports, Letters, List of Officers and Committee Chairs
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1993-1994, TD(3), Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 031:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Professional Recruitment Coordinator (SPRC), 1993-1994, TD(4) (Box-folder 031:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affirmative Action Committee Reports, 1993-1994, TD(4) (Box-folder 031:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Health Council, 1993-1994, TD(3) (Box-folder 031:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Health Council, 1993-1994, TD(1) (Box-folder 031:031)
  Flyer
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions (VAAHP), 1993-1994, TD(5) (Box-folder 031:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Prevention Advocacy Network (VPAN), 1993-1994, TD(14) (Box-folder 031:033)
  Membership Contact List, Memorandum, Survey Form, Minutes
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Congress of Health Professions, 1993-1994, TD(2) (Box-folder 031:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VANH Administrators, 1993-1994, AD(1) (Box-folder 031:035)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Professional Recognition, 1993-1994, TD(229) (Box-folder 032:001)
  Memoranda, Letters, Senate Bill 396, Reports, Journal Article, House of Delegates Amendment Forms, Newpaper Articles,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Grassroots, 1993-1994, TD(92) (Box-folder 032:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board Meetings, 1993-1994, TD(48) (Box-folder 032:003)
  Minutes, Reports, Letters, Membership Listing
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Finance, 1993-1994, TD(26), AD(8) (Box-folder 032:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1993-1994, TD(33), Pamphlet(2), Booklet(1) (Box-folder 032:005)
  Letters, Bylaws, Virginia Legislative Directory, Biographies of Members of the House of Delegates, House Bill No.312, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Annual Meetings, 1993-1994, TD(25) (Box-folder 032:006)
  Minutes, Reports, Leadership Workshop Participant List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates Report, 1994-1995, TD(70) (Box-folder 033:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure Assessment/ Prefessional Recognition, 1994-1995, TD(6), AD(1) (Box-folder 033:002)
  Minutes, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislative Assistant, 1994-1995, TD(12) (Box-folder 033:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS, 1994-1995, TD(11) (Box-folder 033:004)
  letters, Reports, Newsletter Articles, Flyer
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations (National Nutrition Month), 1994-1995, TD(11), AD(1) (Box-folder 033:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: COP, 1994-1995, TD(6) (Box-folder 033:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Publications, 1994-1995, TD(3) (Box-folder 033:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Lines, 1994-1995, Newsletters(4) (Box-folder 033:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws/Long Range Planning, 1994-1995, TD(4) (Box-folder 033:009)
  Reports, Bylaws Fact Sheet
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Nominations/ Scholarship and Awards, 1994-1995, TD(49) (Box-folder 033:010)
  Letters, Reports, Award Application Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADAF, 1994-1995, TD(9) (Box-folder 033:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affirmative Action, 1994-1995, TD(2) (Box-folder 033:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Carrer Guidance SPRC, 1994-1995, TD(1) (Box-folder 033:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislative Information/Public Policy, 1994-1995, TD(21) (Box-folder 033:014)
  Reports, Memorandum, Registration Forms, Flyer, Lists of U.S. Senates and House of Representatives, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian / RYDY / RYDT, 1994-1995, TD(14) (Box-folder 033:015)
  Letters, Report, Award Nomination Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Administrative Report, 1994-1995, TD(14) (Box-folder 033:016)
  Letters, Reports, Executive Board Members List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1994-1995, TD(4) (Box-folder 033:017)
  Continuing Education Hours, Evaluation Agreement
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: District Presidents Reports, 1994-1995, TD(148), Newsletter(2) (Box-folder 033:018)
  Reports, Letters, TDA Executive Members List,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Annual Meeting Reports, 1994-1995, TD(3) (Box-folder 033:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Professional Recognition, 1994-1995, TD(12), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 033:020)
  Reports, Memorandum, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Alliance Organizations, 1994-1995, TD(10) (Box-folder 033:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1994-1995, TD(1) (Box-folder 033:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA/Other Correspond, 1994-1995, TD(40) (Box-folder 033:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence, 1994-1995, TD(85), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 033:024)
  Letters, Memorandum, Reports, Disclosure Statements
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: President's Correspondence, 1995, TD(25), AD(10) (Box-folder 034:001)
  Letters, Memorandum, Journal Article
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Minutes, 1995, TD(7), AD(1) (Box-folder 034:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Treasurer Reports, 1995, TD(23), AD(31) (Box-folder 034:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Annual Meeting Reports, 1995, TD(5), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 034:004)
  Annual Meeting Genesis of Change, Program Schedules
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Professional Recognition, 1995, TD(40) (Box-folder 034:005)
  Letters, Memorandum, Reports, OAM General Inforamtion Package, Disclosure Statements, SGA Legislative Update
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislative Assistant / Legislative Information and Public Policy, 1995, TD(7) (Box-folder 034:006)
  ADA Legislative Update, Letter, State Government Affair Assessment, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS, 1995, TD(6) (Box-folder 034:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations (National Nutrition Month), 1995, TD(5) (Box-folder 034:008)
  Reports, Letter, Public Relations/Media Activity Reporting Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Lobbyist, 1995, TD(14) (Box-folder 034:009)
  Letters, Lobbyist Registration Forms, Lobbying Disclosure and Regulation Act
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates Reports, 1995, TD(5) (Box-folder 034:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1995, TD(1) (Box-folder 034:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Lines, 1995, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 034:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws / Long Range Planning Committee, 1995, TD(25) (Box-folder 034:013)
  Reports, Bylaws, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Nominations / Scholarships and Awards, 1995, TD(6) (Box-folder 034:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADAF, 1995, TD(1) (Box-folder 034:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian, 1995, TD(51) (Box-folder 034:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Administrative Reports, 1995, TD(3) (Box-folder 034:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1995, TD(2) (Box-folder 034:018)
  Continuing Education Hours
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: District President's Reports, 1995, TD(19) (Box-folder 034:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Alliance Organizations, 1995, TD(2) (Box-folder 034:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1995, TD(1) (Box-folder 034:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Correspondence, 1995, TD(30), Newspaper Articles(9), Flyers(3), AD(4), Booklet(1) (Box-folder 034:022)
  Letters, Reports, List of Charter Fellows, List of the Outstanding Dietetic Educator Award, Psychologically Speaking with Dr. Jack Singer, Nutrition and Health Resource Guide for Teachers
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence, 1999, TD(124), AD(2), Newspaper Clippings(3) (Box-folder 034:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 1964, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 035:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 1969, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 035:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 1981, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 035:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 1982, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 035:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 1986, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 036:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 1988, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 036:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Officer's Manual, 2000, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 036:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: ADA Star, 1937, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: The RIDA Bugle (Vol. 1, No. 3), 1939, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: The RIDA Bugle (Vol. 2, No. 2), April, 1940, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 5, No. 3), June, 1946, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 5, No. 4), November, 1946, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 6, No. 1), Winter, 1947, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 6, No. 4), Spring, 1947, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 6, No. 4), Summer, 1947, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 7, No. 1), Fall, 1947, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 8, No. 4), October, 1948, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 9, No. 1), March, 1949, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 9, No. 2), July, 1949, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 10, No. 1), January, 1950, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:013)